# **JEAN SUSOR**

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER



## **SUMMARY**

I'm currently working freelance as a Web Developer. I can do backend using NodeJS but I am more comfortable working as Frontend Angular Developer. Previously, I always worked with a team so I'm already used to Git's Version Control. I am a team player and can communicate effectively.

As a Wordpress Administrator before, I know a website's best practices, SEO, design to enhance customer satisfaction and to high rank in Google.



# CONTACT

Phone Email

0917080622 jlalama2011@gmail.com

**Address** 

Dúbravica, Slovakia

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jean-susor/

**Github** 

https://github.com/Puffyfish



# **EDUCATION**

Mar 2023 Angular Udemy

Jan 2022 Web Development Udemy

April 2017 Web Designing
Informatics Computer Technology

**2005 - 2009 BS Nursing** Cebu Normal University



## **TECH STACK**

- HTML
- Angular
- ExpressJS

- CSS
- NodeJS
- MongoDB

- Javascript
- Typescript



# **PROJECTS**

## Report Log App

April 2023

HtML, SCSS, Javascript, Angular, MySql, PHP

- Overall design of website using Angular Material
- · Landing page which was created with CSS
- Integration of frontend to backend
- Creating the components for the individual pages

#### Daily Todo App

April 2023

HtML, CSS, Javascript, Angular, Angular Material

- basic to-do app that has to-do lists per project
- · overall design of the app using Angular Material
- · creating database using json-server

#### Dashboard Website

Sep 2022

Javascript, MongoDB, ExpressJS, NodeJS

-won first place in W3Schools 2021 Challenge

- · Overall design
- Responsible for CRUD operations of data
- · Setting the routes using ExpressJS
- Demonstrating data using ChartJS
- Managing MongDB to handle data

### Recipe Website

June 2022

HtML, CSS, Javascript -won third place in W3Schools 2021 Challenge

- · overall design of website
- popup feature of recipes

# **JEAN SUSOR**

## HTTPS://PUFFYFISH.GITHUB.IO/PORTFOLIO/

# WORK EXPERIENCE

**Web Developer** 

O 2022 - present

Part-time Freelancer

• I create websites using the MEAN - stack.

**Wordpress Website Manager** 

0 2020 - 2021

Lab41 (remote work)

- Improve different websites' SEO
- Design and edit Wordpress websites' pages layout
- Add writers' articles on to our clients' websites
- Track keywords and guest posts using Excel

**Warehouse Admin Staff** 

0 2016 - 2018

Chef Direct, Booker Group, United Kingdom

- Manage ingoing and outgoing deliveries using the company's CRM
- Organize receipts and paperworks for proper documentation
- Contacts suppliers daily to solve delivery problems

**Stock Control Administrator** 

0 2014 - 2016

Kreemar Enterprises, Philippines

- Track daily business operations through a CRM
- Communicate with main suppliers
- Create monthly reports of profits and expenditures

**Staff Nurse** 

2013 - 2014

Vicente Sotto Memorial Medical Center, Philippines

- staff nurse in Operating Room
- staff nurse in Emergency Room
- · staff nurse in the Medical Ward
- staff nurse in the OB ward

# **JEAN SUSOR**

## HTTPS://PUFFYFISH.GITHUB.IO/PORTFOLIO/



#### **ANGULAR**



Certificate no: UC-13fc8520-4a25-4ab3-afe1-195b9fe6bccb
Certificate url: ude.my/UC-13fc8520-4a26-4ab3-afe1-195b9fe6bccb
Reference Number: 0004

CERTIFICATE OF COMPLETION

# Angular - The Complete Guide (2023 Edition)

Instructors Maximilian Schwarzmüller

## Jean Ialaine Susor

Date March 26, 2023 Length 34.5 total hours

#### > JAVASCRIPT





# **CERTIFICATE OF COMPLETION**

This certifies that

**Jean Susor** 

has completed the necessary courses of study and passed

the W3Schools' JavaScript exams and is hereby declared a

**Certified JavaScript Developer** 

with fundamental knowledge of web development using JavaScript and the HTML DOM.

Issued March 15, 2023

Thomas Thorsell-Arntsen for W3schools.com

Thouas I porel

Verify completion at https://verify.w3schools.com/1NIDVYAYGT